Anjaneyulu Talari



urstalari@gmail.com



+919177091030



linkedin.com/in/anjan-talari

Summary

With 11+ years of experience in the IT industry, including 3+ years of experience as an IT Manager. Expertise in Design and Implementation of Infrastructure, Networking, and IT Operations. Knowledge of AWS Cloud, Security, and SQL.

Experience



Information Technology Manager

Vijaya Diagnostic Centre Limited

Feb 2022 - Present (5 months +)

Handling On-premises data center, Including 15+ Production servers.

Design and Implementation of infrastructure and Networking as per the Organization's requirements.

Managed a team of 20 L1, and L2 Engineers to achieve 100% SLAs.

Assistant It Manager

Paradise Food Court Pvt. Ltd (Paradise Biryani)

Jan 2020 - Jan 2022 (2 years 1 month)

Designed and Build AWS infra for 50+ branches and addressed L1 production issues.

Modified existing standalone network from a single link to an auto-failover link within the budget and achieved 98% uptime.

Handling 20+ on-premises Production Servers and Cloud infrastructure.

Established secure Site 2 Site connection between On-premises to AWS cloud.

QUESS Network Engineer

Quess Corp Limited

Mar 2019 - Jan 2020 (11 months)

Managed 400+ L3 Network devices and L2 Network devices, awarded star of the guarter for achieving 99.9% uptime.

More than 100+ PE(Planned Events) completed Successfully.

Team coordination and vendor coordination on day-to-day operation. Attending Weekly reviews and achieving target dates.

Information Technology Executive

Wonderla Holidays Ltd.

Jan 2017 - Mar 2019 (2 years 3 months)

Design and build Enterprise infrastructure and Networking with 99% uptime to the operations.

Handled 300+ IT systems with help of 3 L1 Engineers.

Zero downtown for billing counter with BCP Plan.

Provided infrastructure and Network requirements for Implemented Disaster recovery on a cloud platform

Network Engineer

Trimax IT Infrastructure & Services Ltd, GI Group, CMC Ltd (Client-RIL)

Apr 2014 - Dec 2016 (2 years 9 months)

Closely worked with the operation team and addressed their technical issues based on the SLAs.

Trained L1 Technical engineers and motivate them to achieve 99% SLAs.

Handled 200 + IT equipment including servers, desktops, Routers, Switches, ADSL modems, and Access Points.

TCP/IP, DNS, DHCP, ADDC, Citrix Client, Outlook, Windows OS, Auto CAD, etc

Technical Support Engineer

Manappuram Finance Limited

Oct 2010 - Feb 2014 (3 years 5 months)

L1, L2 Technical support for 2 Clusters LAN, WAN, Windows, Linux, VPN-Client, Domain, SLAs, and

L1 Technical Support for 30 branches where handled Desktops, Printers, Scanners. LAN, Users & Groups.

Education



S.K University - CVLNR Inst Of Sci & Tech

Master of Computer Application (MCA)

Licenses & Certifications

☑ ITIL Foundation Level - PositiveEdge Solutions

Cisco Certified Network Associate Industrial (CCNA I) - Pearson India

Skills

Amazon Web Services (AWS) • Networking • IT Infrastructure Management • Windows • Office 365 Administration

Honors & Awards



Dum Award From CTO - Paradise Food Court Pvt. Ltd (Paradise Biryani)

Aug 2021

Openness to learning new skills / Knowledge